https://www.designer-websites.co.uk/privacy

We are Hiring! find out more
We are looking for full-time web developers and support roles. Apply Now!01446 339050HomeWhat We Do Our Website Services Professional Website DesignEcommerce WebsitesWebsite OptimisationBlog DevelopmentWebsite HostingAMP DevelopmentDigital MarketingSearch Engine OptimisationContent StrategySocial Media ManagementPPC AdvertisingEmail MarketingPhoto & Video Photography For WebsitesVideography For BusinessDrone Filming & Aerial Photos360° Video & Street ViewBranding & DesignBrand DevelopmentUser Interface DesignDesign For PrintSystems DevelopmentBespoke Web-based SolutionsComplex API IntegrationsWhite Label SolutionsPayment IntegrationProgressive Web Apps Talk to us today to discover how we can grow your business online. 01446 339050Our WorkCareersContact UsGet a Quote >Home > Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyWe do not automatically collect any personally identifiable information about users of this website. We will only record your personal details if you provide them voluntarily via one of the contact forms on our website. We also collate general aggregate information about use of the website for statistical purposes (see ‘Google Analytics’, below).The information we collect If you choose to contact us using one of the contact forms on this website, we may collect the following details (if you choose to provide them): Your nameYour company nameYour email addressYour telephone numberYour reasons for contacting Designer WebsitesAny other information that you choose to submit to us When you submit information via one of our online enquiry forms, the information is sent to us via email (rather than being stored in a database). These emails are generally deleted after 12 months unless there is a specific reason for us to retain your email beyond that period. What we do with your information If you provide information to us via our contact forms, we will only use that information to respond to your enquiry (e.g. emailing you a quotation for our services).
Unless you give us permission to do so, we will not: Add you to any mailing listsSend you correspondence that is unrelated to your reasons for contacting usShare your details with a third partySecurityWe endeavour to keep all sensitive information as secure as possible. Our servers are house in a purpose-built secure data centre that uses firewalls, secure access and activity logging. We have a designated Data Protection Officer, and we also have defined procedures in place that govern how we track and use your data.Accessing your personal information You have the right to:Ask to see what personal data (if any) we hold on you – in most cases, we can provide this data for free within 1 month of receiving your requestCorrect any false, outdated or incomplete data we hold on youRequest that we delete any/all personal data we hold on you – such requests will be honoured unless we have a legitimate reason for refusalWithdraw any permissions you have given us in the past (e.g. if you give us permission to send you news updates via email, you can change your mind at any time) If you wish to do any of the above, please email our Data Protection Officer at dpo@designer-websites.co.uk. Cookies policyOur website uses cookies – view our cookies policy here.Google Analytics Like many website owners, we use Google Analytics to monitor the performance of our site. This tool does not collect any personally identifiable information, but if you would prefer not to be included in our Analytics data, you can download Google’s opt-out browser add-on here.
See also: Google Analytics – Safeguarding Your Data. Any questions?You can discuss our privacy policy with our Data Protection Officer via email at dpo@designer-websites.co.uk. If you believe you have received unsolicited email from Designer Websites, please send your complaint to our Data Protection Officer along with a copy of the unsolicited email and we will do everything we can to ensure that this does not happen again. We reserve the right to change the wording of this policy at any time. Please check this page regularly to ensure that you are familiar with the latest version of our privacy policy.About usNewsMeet The TeamCareersTermsPrivacy PolicyCookies PolicySitemapFind usDesigner Websites Ltd Sully Moors Road, Sully
Vale of Glamorgan
South Wales
CF64 5RP Talk to us + 44 (0)1446 339050info@designer-websites.co.ukFollow us©  Designer Websites Ltd 2020. All rights reservedIntelligent digital solutions by experienced developers
